http://paralegaltoday.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
October 10, 2020
Posts
Comments
Paralegal TodayThe Online Information Source for Paralegal Professionals
Contact Us
Conexion International Media, Inc.
Our policy regarding use of your personal information
Paralegal Today magazine (“we,” “us,” “our”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personally identifiable information. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on this site (“Site”) and how such information may be used and/or shared with others. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through this Site and not through any other sources.
YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE USE IT
This Site collects two kinds of information:
(1) Information that personally identifies you (such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address); and
(2) Information that does not personally identify you (such as the number of users who log on to the Site on a daily basis).
As a general policy, no personally identifiable information is automatically collected from your visit to this Site. LITIGATION SUPPORT TODAY only collects and retains personal information that you provide to us voluntarily. In certain circumstances, you may be asked to provide us with some personally identifiable information about yourself in order to use specific features on the Site, such as sweepstakes, contests, surveys and other promotions. Such information may include contact information, and other information as we may require. The personally identifiable information you submit will be used to carry out your requests and respond to your inquiries. To accomplish this, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties that perform functions on our behalf (or on behalf of our partners), such as companies or individuals that deliver merchandise, participate in our promotions, administer our promotions, provide marketing or promotional assistance, analyze data or provide customer service. In that case, such information will be shared only to the extent they need such information to perform their functions. Your personally identifiable information may also be used by us or shared with our parent company and affiliates to provide you with product information, and promotional and other offers. However, you may always direct us (by contacting us at the address listed below) not to share your personally identifiable information with these parties or not to use your personally identifiable information to provide you with information or offers.
We may also use your information as otherwise disclosed at the point where such information is collected or in any additional terms and conditions applicable to the particular feature of the Site. Except as provided herein, your personally identifiable information will not be supplied to any third parties without prior approval from you. From time to time, we may collect non-personally identifiable information from you through the standard operation of our servers. Such information can include the type of browser being used, the operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and the number of users that visit a specific page on the Site and the character and duration of such visits. This information may be used to help analyze site traffic and improve our services. We may also aggregate such information to create statistical data and share it with potential advertisers, partners, affiliates and other third parties. At no point, however, will the aggregated information personally identify you.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information if we are required to do so or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary in order to:
(a) fulfill a government request;
(b) conform with the requirements of the law;
(c) comply with legal process served on us;
(d) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Paralegal Today, Conexion International Media, Inc. and its affiliates, this Site, or its users; or
(e) in an emergency to protect the welfare of our users or the general public.
We may also transfer personally identifiable information to another entity in the event of certain corporate transactions, such as a merger, consolidation, sale of assets or corporate division or other fundamental corporate change. IP ADDRESS An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. Web servers, the big computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, reporting aggregate information to our advertisers, and to track Site usage. When visitors request pages from the Site, our servers log the visitors’ IP addresses. It is not our practice to link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a visitor’s session will be logged, but the visitor remains anonymous to us. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor only when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Site’s policies or to protect our service, customers, the Site, or others.
COOKIES
“Cookies” are small text files from a Web site that are stored on your hard drive. These small text files make using a Web site more convenient by saving your passwords and preferences for you. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. We may analyze the information derived from these cookies and match such information with data provided by you or another party. We may provide our analysis and certain non- personally identifiable information to potential partners, advertisers (who may use this information to provide advertisements tailored to your interests) or other third parties, but we will not disclose any personally identifiable information, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. Also, we may allow third parties that serve advertisements on our Site (including our promotion partners) to place and access cookies on your computer, but they will not be able to access our cookies. The use of cookies by such third parties is not subject to our Privacy Policy, but is subject to their own respective privacy policies. You can have the option of deciding whether or not to accept a cookie by resetting your browser to notify you whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard drive. You may also delete a cookie manually from your hard drive. Please note, however, that some parts of this Site will not function properly or will be considerably slower if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable your cookies settings.
KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION SECURE
We have reasonable and appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, information is provided at your own risk; we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.
LINKS
This Site may contain links to other web sites that we do not control or maintain. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by these third party web sites. We encourage you to note when you leave this Site and to read the privacy statements of such other web sites before submitting any personally identifiable information.
CONTACT INFORMATION
If you have questions or comments about our privacy practices, or if you wish to review/amend any personally identifiable information you have provided or wish to opt-out of any further promotional efforts or sharing of information, you can contact us at:
Company Privacy Policy, Attn: Webmaster
Conexion International Media, Inc.
The world's leading aerospace company is seeking a Litigation Paralegal: to join the Law Department in our … Continue
International Practice Management Association (IPMA)
American Association for Paralegal Education (AAfPE)
Upcoming Events
ALA 2019 Annual Conference & ExpoEvent Description:
Takes place April 14 - 17, Read more
1
Follow Us!
Navigation Help
Sitemap
Return to top of page | Site Map
Copyright © 2020 · Paralegal Today · Website by YourWebsiteDude.com · Log in
